(シカマル)お～い いの いるか？
UNOFFICIAL LEAF VILLAGE MASCOT KONORIN
Hey Ino…you here?
(いの)なに？
２人揃ってどうしたの？
Yeah? What are you two
doing together?
こないだ
カカシ先生から言われた あれ➡
Remember what Kakashi Sensei
said last time?
覚えてるだろ？
((カカシ : キミたちには
ナルトとヒナタの結婚祝いを→
I am giving you
a secret mission
(独自に用意するという
極秘任務を与える))
in which you shall each prepare
a congratulatory gift for
Naruto and Hinata's wedding.
もちろんよ。
で それがどうしたの？
Of course!
And? What about it?
ああ 贈り物の打ち合わせを
しようと思ってよ。
Oh… I thought we'd discuss
what to get them.
残念！ あいにく 私もう
めぼしいものは決めてあるし→
Oh, sorry!
I've got something great
picked out already
ちょうど そのお店に
行くとこなの。
and I'm about to go
to the store.
どこだ？ 俺たちも行く。
ダメよ！
Which store?
We'll go with you!
No, you aren't!
お店かぶるのとか ありえない！
We can't get gifts from
the same store.
あんたたちは あんたたちで考えて
じゃあね！
You two can think of
something on your own!
Later!
What are we gonna do?
どうしたもんかな。
(チョウジ)店員さん！
Excuse me, Miss!
I'd like to get some ice cream
for dessert.
デザートのアイスクリームちょうだい。
シカマルは？
What about you, Shikamaru?
None for me.
いや 俺はいい。
相変わらず よく食うな。
You sure can eat, though…
胃腸だけは
ガキの頃と同じじゃねえか。
Your appetite hasn't changed
since you were a kid.
But these days,
I've started liking thigh meat,
でも 最近は もも肉とか→
as well as meat that's really rare,
赤身のお肉も
おいしくなってきたから→
だいぶ 大人になったと思うよ。
so I think I'm going towards
more grown-up tastes.
舌の問題かよ。
So it's your taste buds?
でよ さっきの話なんだが
どうする？
Anyway, getting back
to the subject.
やっぱ アイスより
ゆずシャーベットだったかな？
Maybe yuzu sorbet would've
been better than ice cream…
No! I'm talking about the wedding gift
for Naruto and Hinata!
違ぇよ！
ナルトたちへの結婚祝いの話だ！
ああ なんだそっちか。
Oh that.
Here's your ice cream.
(大蛇丸)アイス お待ちどおさま。
きたきた！
Oh, it's here!
Judging from Ino's attitude,
she'll be no help…
いののやつ あの調子じゃ
力になってくれそうにねえ。
If this keeps going,
このままじゃ
俺たちだけ 祝いの品を→
we might be the only ones
who can't find a present.
用意できねえってことも
ありうるぞ。
俺たちって どういうこと？
What do you mean by "we"?
僕は もう 決めてるんだけど。
I've already picked
something out.
ほ… ほんとかよ！
何にするんだ？
R-Really?!
What are you getting?
うん ２人には
これをあげようかと思ってるんだ。
I'm thinking about
giving them this.
SATOCHO DINNER GIFT CERTIFICATE
Hey, this is a—!
お前 これって…。
うん お食事券！
SATOCHO DINNER GIFT CERTIFICATE
Yup, a gift certificate
for a dinner!
And it's not just for
an average diner!
しかも ただのお食事券じゃねえ。
It's a gift certificate for
a super-fancy teahouse
火影クラスのお偉い人しか
行くことのない→
that VIPs like
the Hokage go to!
超高級料亭の
お食事券じゃねえか。
Well, it is a special occasion…
お祝いだからね。
《クッ どういうことだ？
What's going on?!
あのチョウジが選んだものなのに
贈り物としては最高じゃねえか。
This is Choji…
And he chose the perfect gift!
ふだんでは行けないような店で
食事をするというのは→
Having dinner in a restaurant
you wouldn't normally be able to go to
お祝い感があるし
２人の思い出に強く残る。
is special and really memorable
for a couple!
これほど気のきいた結婚祝いは
なかなかねえ。
Not a lot of gifts would have
as much impact!
それに
いくらお祝いだからといって→
And even if this was
for a special occasion…
Choji's willing to part
with a gift certificate
あのチョウジが
そんないい店のお食事券を→
to a super-fancy restaurant,
just like that?
躊躇なく手放すだと？》
店員さん アイスおかわり。
Miss, may I have another bowl
of ice cream?
《シカマル : お前は本当に
あのチョウジなのか？
Are you really
the Choji I know?!
It's not just your taste buds
that grew up.
チョウジ お前は舌だけでなく
いったい全体→
Have you completely
become an adult?
どこまで大人びちまうんだ？》
What?
(大蛇丸)アイス お待ち。
Here's your ice cream.
It just happened to be
a three-for-one special.
ちょうどそれ
３名１組だったんだよね。
Why is it three to a group?
《よりによって なんで
３名１組なんだよ？
Usually a romantic dinner
is for two.
普通 恋人同士で２名様だとか
そういうことを→
You'd think a fancy restaurant
would be aware of that!
もうちょっと考えろよ 高級料亭。
Choji will tag along
if it's three to a group!
３名様だと チョウジが行くだろうが》
Shikamaru?
What's wrong, Shikamaru?
シカマル？ どうしたの シカマル？
It's nothing…
いや その もしかして
お前も一緒に…。
Are you planning to go too?
Are you joking?
まさか！ いくら僕でも→
Even I know better than to tag along
with some newlyweds…
さすがに新婚の２人と
一緒なわけないよ。
R-Right? Of course you would.
だ だよな。 さすがにそれは…。
I was gonna ask the waitress to
seat me at a different table.
店員さんに頼んで
僕だけ違う席にしてもらうよ。
《行くのかよ！
So, you ARE going?!
Still, this is not the time
to get on Choji's case.
いや チョウジのことを
とやかく言ってる場合じゃねえ。
問題なのは まだ祝いの品を
何も決めてない この俺だ。
I still haven't decided to
what to get them.
And I can't waste a minute
on deciding.
一刻も早く決めねえと。
I'm thinking…
something useful.
実用的なものは
お祝いの感じが薄いし→
A decorative item would just get
in the way if it's not to their taste.
飾り物の趣味が合わなきゃ
邪魔になるだけだ。
Flowers or food would
be gone eventually,
花や食べ物なんかの消えものも→
and it would seem like
a seasonal gift.
まるでお歳暮や
お中元みたいに見えちまう。
Sending them something
is really risky…
やっぱり物を贈るのは
リスキーと言わざるをえねえ。
So that leaves…cash!
だとすると… 現金か！
悪くはねえ。
That's not a bad idea.
They can get whatever they want,
好きなものを選んで
買うことができるし→
and it's way better than getting
something they won't use
使わないものや 他の人と
かぶったものを贈るより→
or something that's identical
to someone else's gift.
よっぽど気がきいてる。
いや しかし考えてみろ。
But wait a minute…
What if I'm the only one
giving them cash?
俺だけが
現金を持っていったら…》
It's not a lot, but please accept it!
((少ねえけど とっとけ))
《ダメだ！
Not good!
Everyone will think I was
the only one too lazy
俺の場合 面倒くさがって
買い物にも行かず→
to go out and buy a gift and
何も考えずに
ただカネだけ出したように→
just gave them cash
without thinking.
思われちまわねえか？》
Shikamaru, you okay?
シカマル 大丈夫？
U-Uh, yeah… I just felt a chill.
あ ああ ちょっと寒気がな。
ごめん。
Sorry, did you get cold
from watching me eat
僕がアイス食べまくるの見てたら
寒くなっちゃった？
all that ice cream?
そうじゃねえが…。
That's not it…
焼肉で ほてった体には
ちょうどいいよ。
I got hot from eating
all that barbecue,
so it was just what I needed.
Besides, I'm the kinda guy
who can eat ice cream
それに僕は たとえ
雪国を旅していたとしても→
even if I'm traveling
in snow country!
あえて アイスを買って
食べるタイプの男だからね。
My appetite beats
the cold every time.
食欲は 寒さを凌駕するんだ。
Damn it, no one can
beat your appetite—
まったく お前の食欲には
ついていけね…。
チョウジ お前 今 なんて言った？
Choji! What did you just say?!
食欲は寒さを凌駕するって。
My appetite beats the cold?
No, before that!
違う その前だ！ 雪国を…。
What about snow country?
Oh…
あ～ 雪国を旅していても
アイスを食べるって。
I can eat ice cream even if
I'm traveling in snow country…
それだ！
That's it!
Steam and Food Pills
A honeymoon?
新婚旅行？
Yeah… I'm gonna gift Naruto
and Hinata a honeymoon.
ああ ナルトとヒナタに
新婚旅行をプレゼントするんだ。
So where are you off to now?
で これからどこへ行くの？
I have to decide on a place,
and go check it out.
旅先を決めて できれば
下見まで済ましておきてえな。
それと ヒナタのことを考えると→
And I need to get
a woman's point of view
女の目線での意見も
聞いておきてえ。
so I can get a sense of
what Hinata might like.
いのでもいれば いいんだが。
いた！
If only Ino were here…
There she is!
え？
(テマリ)あ…。
よ よう 久しぶりだな。
あんとき以来か。
H-Hey…
It's been awhile…
ever since that day, huh?
あ ああ お前たちこそ
何をしているんだ？
Y-Yeah.
What are you guys up to?
ちょ ちょっとな ２人で昼メシを…
お前は？
Uh, stuff…We just had
some lunch. And you?
わ 私は中忍試験の
打ち合わせついでに→
I'm here to discuss
the Chunin Exams
挨拶回りといったところだ。
お おお そうか。
and making my rounds
to people…
O-Oh…that so?
な なんだよ 「いた！」って
俺は てっきり いのかと。
What the hell?!
I thought you meant
Ino was there…
でも 女の子の意見っていうなら→
You said
a "woman's point of view,"
べつに いのじゃなくても
いいじゃない。
so it doesn't have to be Ino.
But she's a warrior-type
to the core.
しかし あいつは
根っからの武闘派だぞ。
結婚祝いの話なんかしたら…。
I can't talk to her about
a wedding gift…
((なに？
結婚祝いに新婚旅行？
What?
A honeymoon as
a wedding gift?
(のん気でくだらないことを
考えてるんだな))
Talk about a silly
and pathetic idea.
な～んて返ってくるのは
目に見えてんだろうが。
I just know she'd say
something like that.
そんなこと言ったら
いのだって怪しいもんだよ。
Wouldn't that apply
to Ino as well?
おい ２人でコソコソと怪しいな。
Hey, what're you two
whispering about?
Oh, it's nothing…
いや べつに なにも…。
シカマルが相談したいことが
あるみたいなんだけど。
I think Shikamaru wants to talk
to you about something.
そ 相談？
T-Talk to me?
Maybe…next time…
we can go get a bite to eat.
((今度 その なんだ…
メシでも一緒にどうだ？))
そ… 相談って なんだ？
T-Talk about what?
チョウジ！ お前…。
Damn it, Choji!
《ここで まさか→
I can't come out and
say something like,
テマリに新婚旅行の相談をしても
無理っぽいなんて言えねえよな》
"It's no use talking to Temari
about honeymoons."
まぁ… しかたねえな。
ん？
Well…
I guess have no choice…
いや その なんだ…。
Well, you see…
真剣に新婚旅行について
考えてるんだがよ。
I'm seriously thinking about
a honeymoon.
So, if it were you,
where would you like to go?
例えば お前はどこがいいと思う？
えぇっ!? し し し… 新婚旅行？
ど… どうした!?
Huh?!
A-A honeymoon?!
W-What's the matter?
い… いや し… 新婚旅行か。
N-Nothing.
A honeymoon, huh?
なんで その…
わ… 私に聞くんだ？
W-Why would you ask me that?
えっ？ そりゃ とりあえず…。
Huh? Well, I just figured…
《ちょっと待て…。
Wait a second.
ここで
とりあえず 誰でもいいから→
I can't come out and say
it really doesn't matter who,
女の意見が聞きたいなんて
いくらなんでも言えねえ》
I just need
a woman's opinion, can I?
お前に聞くのが一番かな と
思ったから だな。
I figured you'd be
the best one to ask.
わ わ… 私が い… 一番!?
I-I'm the best one?
そうか… じゃあ しかたないな。
I-I see.
O-Okay then,
I'll hear you out.
ちゃんと聞こう。
お… おう！
O-Oh…
俺としては 温泉旅館なんかで
のんびりってのが→
Well, I thought a hot spring
would be nice and relaxing…
いいんじゃねえかと
考えてるんだが→
そういうのって
じじくせぇかな？
Does that sound like something
an old man would like?
あ… あぁ
いいんじゃないか？ 温泉。
No, a hot spring sounds great!
そうか？ よかったぜ！
Really? Awesome!
うまい飯に温泉 最高だよな！
Good food and hot springs…
perfect, right?
《よかった！ とりあえず
意見も聞けたし これで…》
Good. At least I got confirmation.
So now…
あとは どこの旅館にするか だね。
Now you have to
choose where, right?
えっ？ あぁ そうだな。
簡単に下見でも行っとくか。
Huh? Oh, yeah.
Maybe we can check some out.
まだ 日も高いし
今から行っちゃえば？
It's still early.
Why not go now?
おう そうだな じゃあ…。
Yeah, that's true. Then…
僕は 甘栗甘に行くから
２人で行ってきなよ。
I'm going to Amaguriama.
So why don't you two go?
(テマリ/シカマル)えっ!?
Huh?!
う～ん ごめん 僕 どうしても
食後のデザートを食べたくてさ。
Sorry, I just have to have
some dessert after eating!
さっき 食ったじゃねえか！
You just ate!
I always save room for dessert.
デザートは別腹なんだよ。
You just filled that room earlier!
だから さっき その別腹に
しこたま入れただろ！
《あぁ バカ野郎…
チョウジが勝手なこと言うから→
You idiot!
Because of Choji's big mouth,
テマリのやつ 怒って
顔を赤くしてるじゃねえか！》
Temari's standing there
red-faced and upset!
いや その なんだ…。
Sorry, Choji didn't mean to
get you upset or anything.
チョウジも悪気があって
言い出したわけじゃねえんだ。
ほら… 新婚旅行だから→
Since we're talking
about honeymoons,
俺１人じゃ意味がないだろう
と 思ってだな…。
he figured there's no sense
I go alone.
うん そうだよ。
Yeah, that's right.
新婚旅行なんだから
２人で行ったほうがいいよ。
A honeymoon is meant for two,
so you guys should go.
それじゃ お二人さん
僕は もう行くね。
Okay, you two. I'm off.
Hey, uh…Mr. C-Choji?!
あっ！ チョ… チョウジさん!!
《なんつうか その…
どうすんだ？ これ！》
What am I supposed to do now?
行く。
I'll go with you.
へっ？
Huh?
《どうして こうなった？
なんなんだ？ この謎の緊張感は。
How did it turn out like this?
W-What's with this strange
nervousness?
とにかく ナルトとヒナタの結婚祝いを→
Anyway, I never expected
Temari to help me out
テマリが協力してくれるのは
予想外だ。
with choosing a wedding gift
for Naruto and Hinata.
However…
しかし なんで
さっきから黙りっぱなしなんだ!?
Why is she so silent
all of a sudden?
I can't get a read
on her at all!
まったく読めねえ…。
First, I have to get her
out of her bad mood.
まずは テマリの機嫌を
取り戻さないと！》
な… なぁ せ… せっかくだし
どっか 寄ってみるか？
W-Well… Since we're out…
should we stop by
a couple places?
あ… あぁ そうだな。
O-Oh, sure…
あ…。
ん？
HIT THE TARGET
珍しいな お前が外すなんて。
That's rare of you to miss.
あれ？
フフフッ！
What?!
すまねえ これしか獲れなくて。
フフッ！
Sorry…
This was all I could win.
《よく わかんねえが
機嫌は直ったみてぇだな》
I'm not completely sure,
but I think she's in
a good mood now.
《よかった！ まだ あった。
Thank goodness!
It's still here!
これしかない と
思ってたんだよね！
I knew it was
the perfect wedding gift.
かわいいし
使い勝手はよさそうだし→
It's cute and simple.
なにより 一点ものだし！
It's one of a kind!
I had to get money
from my savings,
その分 貯金を下ろさなきゃ
ダメだったけど→
これなら ヒナタも
絶対 喜んでくれるはず！
but I know Hinata
will love it!
とにかく 私からのお祝いは
これで決まり！》
Anyway, my wedding gift
to them is set!
(サクラ)あ… いのじゃない！
奇遇ね。
I-Ino…
Imagine seeing you here.
そっちこそ！
こんな所で会うとはね。
I can say the same about you.
《まさか…》
《こいつも…》
– No way!
– She isn't—!
そ… そういえば
ナルトには 最近 会った？
B-By the way, have you seen
Naruto lately?
No, not at all.
ううん 全然。
あのナルトが結婚だもんね！
Imagine that,
Naruto getting married.
昔は あんたのこと
追っかけてたのに。
He used to be crazy
about you long ago.
それは 子供のときの話でしょ。
That was back when
we were kids.
ヒナタと一緒になれて
本当によかったわよ。
I'm really happy
he and Hinata are together.
《間違いない！》
《こいつも…》
There's no mistake…
She's also…
《２人 : これを
結婚祝いに贈るつもりだ！》
– planning on that for a wedding gift!
《サクラの隙を突いて
この写真立てを手に入れなきゃ！
I have to get this picture frame
before her!
But how…?
でも どうしたら… あっ！》
あぁ サクラ…
もしかして あんた これを→
Hey Sakura, were you planning
on getting this
ナルトとヒナタの結婚祝いにしようとか
考えてるんじゃないの？
for Naruto and Hinata?
《そうよ
この女のプライドを挑発して→
Huh?
That's right! I have to provoke her
買う気をなくさせればいいんだ》
and make her
too proud to buy it.
あぁ それは ありえないか！
そんなダサい贈り物なんてね。
That's impossible, right?
You wouldn't get something
that tacky, would you?
《挑発にのっちゃ ダメよ！
I'm not gonna fall for it.
この女 写真立てをディスって→
This woman's trying to diss
that picture frame,
私の買う気を
削ごうとしてるだけ》
so I won't buy it.
何 言ってるのよ？
What are you talking about?
あんただって
さっき 買おうとしてたんでしょ。
You were totally about
to buy it earlier…
えっ!? それは…。
Th-That's…
ダサいと思ってるものを
わざわざ買おうとするなんて→
Why would you even think about
buying something tacky? How stupid!
バッカじゃないの!?
バカ!?
Stupid?!
私は買うなんて言ってないでしょ
そ… そうよ！
I didn't say
I was going to buy it!
I was just gonna move it
out of the way
邪魔なゴミだなと思って
どかそうとしただけ。
because it's trash.
ほ… ほんと あんたって
バカ力なだけで センスないわよね！
Really, you may have
brute strength,
but you have no taste at all!
誰が バカ力ですって!?
Brute strength?!
Talk about
a lame comparison!
そんな苦しい言い訳
通用するわけ ないでしょ！
あの… お客様！ 他のお客様の
ご迷惑になりますので。
Excuse me!
You're annoying
the other customers.
ほら いの！
あんたのせいで迷惑だって。
See, Ino!
You're annoying the others!
あんたが
ギャーギャー騒いだせいでしょ！
You're the one who's yelling!
元はといえば あんたでしょ！
You started it!
これは 私のものよ！
私の！
This is mine!
Hey, that's mine!
私が 先に見つけたんじゃないの！
ちょっと！ 離しなさい!!
I found it first!
Now, now…
Please don't pull so hard,
or else—!
お客様！ そんなに すごい力で
引っ張ったら…。
(２人)うるさい！
– Shut up!
(いの)ふざけんじゃないわよ！
You've got some nerve!
あんたのせいで
追い出されちゃったじゃない！
Because of you,
we got kicked out!
That's my line!
それは こっちのセリフよ！
You have no sense
of mutual compromise!
だいたい あんたは譲り合いの精神
ってもんが ないのよ！
You have no regard for anyone,
you have no chest,
気がきかない 胸もない
あるのは バカ力だけ！
all you have is brute strength!
はぁ!?
胸は 今 関係ないでしょ！
Huh?!
My chest has nothing
to do with this!
何から何まで
私に勝てないからって→
There is nothing you
can beat me in,
so you always try to bring up
something unrelated! You should stop that.
関係ない話に
持っていこうとするのやめたら？
フン！ 勝てないとか
意味わかんない。
I don't know the meaning
of not winning.
And I win hands down
in femininity.
女らしさでは
確実に 私が勝ってますけど。
Feminine?!
女らしい!? どこが？
まぁ まぁ まぁ！
You? How?
Now, now…
Stop your fighting, you two.
２人とも ケンカはやめなよ。
チョウジ！ いいとこに来た。
Choji! Perfect timing!
Who's more feminine?
Me or Sakura?!
サクラと私
どっちが女らしいと思う？
You can't just ask something
like that out of the blue…
えっ!?
そんなの 突然 聞かれても…。
フフッ… 同じ班だったチョウジに
ひいきされない時点で→
Even your own teammate, Choji,
won't pick you. How sad!
悲しすぎるじゃない。
はぁ!?
Huh?!
Choji's not on your team,
違う班のチョウジに お世辞すら
言ってもらえない時点で→
but he won't even try to
flatter you. That is so sad!
痛すぎるでしょ！
ちょ ちょ ちょ… やめてよ。
H-Hey, cut it out.
Hmm… Okay then…
じゃあさ そんなに知りたいなら
試してみればいいじゃない？
If you want to know,
why don't you put it to a test.
(２人)試す？
– A test?
Personally, I think someone who
can cook is very feminine.
僕だったら 料理作れる人のほうが
女らしいって考えちゃうね。
So maybe you should see
who cooks better?
だから 料理を比べてみれば
いいんじゃない？
Okay, let's begin
the challenge!
それじゃあ
勝負を始めましょう。
The one who makes
the tastiest food pills wins.
より おいしい兵糧丸を
作ったほうが 勝利よ。
《見てなさい サクラ！
You just watch, Sakura.
I know what you like
and dislike.
こっちは あんたの好き嫌いは
お見通し。
あんたが ギャフンと言うものを作れば
私の勝ちよ》
I just have to make something
that'll make you gag.
審査は チョウジに任せるわ。
The judge will be Choji.
Huh?! You're not going
to eat it?!
えっ!?
あんたが食べるんじゃないの？
Fine with me!
大丈夫 僕は山ほど
アイスを食べてきたばかりだけど→
I just ate a mountain
of ice cream,
but I always have room
for food pills!
兵糧丸は別腹だから。
ま 待ってよ
チョウジは私の班だったんだし→
W-Wait!
Choji's my teammate.
That gives me the edge!
これじゃあ
私に有利でしょ？
You should be okay with
having the advantage…
なに？ 自分が有利なら
それでいいはずじゃない。
まさか 私を ダウンさせるために→
Don't tell me…
You weren't planning to poison them
to make me sick, were you?
毒でも入れるんじゃ
ないでしょうね？
何にもないわよ
さあ 早く始めましょう。
Like I would!
Come on, let's get started!
Okay, without further ado!
では早速 どっちが女らしいか
兵糧丸対決…。
The food pill contest to see
who's more feminine, begins!
Ready, fight!
レディー ファイト！
Whoa, what's this?!
(チョウジ)おおっと これは！
Instead of using
a mortar and pestle,
あえて すり鉢など使わず
微妙なチャクラコントロールで→
she uses her
fine chakra control
素材の大きさに
変化をつけている。
to get the ingredients
to the desired size.
I can't wait to taste
the sensation
口に入れたときの食感が
楽しみだよ～！
when I put it in my mouth!
Whoa!
うほ～！ 超火力で
一気に素材を加熱している！
She's searing the ingredients
with super-fire power!
サクラが使っているのは
幻の黄金ハチミツ！
Sakura is using some
legendary golden honey.
Ino is using cacao powder.
いのは カカオパウダーか
どっちも捨てがたい！
Both seem irresistible!
Th-This is…?!
こ これは！
こ これは…。
Th-This is…
うお～ うまっ！
Yummy!
う～ ま～ い～ よ～！
So delicious!
このまったりとして
しつこくなく→
Rich, yet not too overpowering…
That indescribable something
舌の上で シャッキリポンと
はじけながらも→
that explodes when
it hits your tongue…
上品な香りの中に
転がるような後味は→
That delicate aroma
and taste that lingers…
It's a treasure chest
of sweetness!
まさに 甘さの宝石箱だよ！
Choji!
チョウジ！
で どっちなの？
So? Which is it?
Which one tastes better?
どっちが
おいしいのよ！
Oh, I wolfed both down,
so I can't tell.
あ いっぺんに食べちゃったから
わかんないや。
でも どっちも
すごくおいしい。
But they were both really…good…
い い… うっ ぶは～！
– Choji!
(２人)チョウジ！
(いの)チョウジ チョウジ！
Choji! Choji!
《僕にも 仲間がいっぱい
できたよ！》
I've made a lot of friends too.
Noooo!
いや～！
チョウジ 死なないで～！
Choji! Don't die!
なんなの これ
走馬灯 走馬灯なの!?
What's happening?
Is his life flashing
before his eyes?
いの やっぱり
毒入れたわね？
Ino!
You did used poison,
didn't you?!
そんなもん入れるか！
あんた 私を何だと思ってるのよ！
You know I wouldn't!
Just who do
you think I am, anyway?!
仲間がいっぱい… できたよ。
I've made…a lot of friends…
まずいわ チョウジの走馬灯が
２周目に突入したわよ！
This is bad!
Choji's delirium is getting worse!
どうする気？
What are you doing?
I have to see what's inside it
before I can treat him.
何が入っているのか
確かめてみないことには→
治療のしようがないわ！
毒が入っていたら
舌が痺れるかもしれないけど。
If there's poison in it,
my tongue will go numb…
だから毒なんて
入ってないってば！
I told you,
there's no poison inside!
あ～ もう！
Damn it!
おいしい！
うん。
It's delicious!
Uh-huh!
なんで…
私 この味 すっごく好き！
Why?
I really love this taste.
私も この味 大好き！
Me too! I love this flavor!
いや～ びっくりしたよ。
Boy, that surprised me.
I ate too many sweets…
甘いもの食べ過ぎて…。
Seems my blood sugar
shot up.
血糖値が大変なことに
なっちゃったみたい。
でも もう大丈夫。
なんだ よかった。
But I'm okay now!
Is that all?
Thank goodness.
ねえ いの なんでわざわざ
私の好きな味にしたの？
Hey, Ino.
Why would you go out of the way
to make something I love?
そりゃあ
あんたの好きな味で→
Well…
I figured if I surprised you with
a flavor you'd love, I'd win.
ギャフンと言わせれば
勝てると思って。
はあ 何それ？
私と同じ作戦じゃない。
What, really?
That was my strategy too!
Huh?! You too?
え？ じゃあ サクラも？
どうりで
私が好きな味だったわけだ。
No wonder
I love how it tastes!
(２人)フフフ！
結局 お互いのこと
お見通しだったわけね。
Ultimately, we saw right
through each other.
それじゃあ お見通しついでに
言いたいことがあるんだけど。
Okay, since we know
each other so well,
there's something
I want to say to you.
なによ？
What is it?
Don't you think we'd find
something even better
私たち２人で
結婚祝いを探せば→
もっといいものが
見つけられると思わない？
if we looked for
a wedding gift together?
ウフフ アハハ！
なによ。
What now?
それも お見通しだから。
I was thinking the same thing.
TOMIYA
あの旅館よさそうだな。
え？
That inn seems nice.
Huh?
《シカマル : さっさと決めねえと→
I'd better hurry up
and choose or
ずっと結婚祝いのことで
ウダウダ悩んじまうぞ。
I'll just keep mulling over
this wedding gift.
I just have to pick something!
思い切って腹くくるしかねえ》
よし 入るぞ！
ええ～！
Okay. Let's go in!
Huh?!
どうした？
これは 下見じゃないのか？
What's the matter?
Weren't we just going to…
look around?
下見だけどよ でも入ってみねえと
決心つかねえだろ。
Yeah, but we have to go inside
or we can't make a decision.
いや しかし
まだ 心の準備が…。
No, but…
I'm not mentally prepared…
《なんだ 心の準備？
What? Mentally prepared?
Is she panicking because
this place too fancy?
あまりに豪華な旅館で
ビビってんのか？》
大丈夫だって とりあえず
入ってから考えよう な？
It's okay.
Temari, let's just go inside
and then we can decide.
I-It'll be too late once
we go inside!
入ってからだと遅いんだ！
雰囲気にながされて
しまうかもしれないから。
I might get caught up
in the mood…
《どういうことだ 雰囲気？
What's she talking about?
The mood?
あの旅館の雰囲気がどうした？
The mood of that inn?
What does she mean
by getting caught up in it?
それに流されるってなんだ？
さっぱりわからねえ》
I don't get it!
お前 まさか！
Hey…you don't…
熱でもあるんじゃねえか？
…have a fever, do you?
わ 私は先に帰るからな！
I-I'm going home!
おい待て じきに暗くなるぞ！
H-Hey, wait!
It's gonna get dark soon!
体調も悪いなら なおさら→
If you're not feeling well,
宿でもとって
休んでかなくちゃなんねえだろ！
we really should book
a room and rest!
待ってくれ！
Please wait!
俺には お前が必要なんだ！
I really…need you!
本当に私でいいのか？
Are you sure…I'm the one?
ああ お前しかいない！
Yeah! You're the only one!
なんつったって 俺じゃ
女湯に入れないからな。
Besides, I can't go into
the women's bath.
え？
テマリ お前が女湯に入って→
What?
Temari, I need you to go
into the women's bath
俺に女湯の様子を
こと細かく報告してくれ。
and report back
every detail to me.
ただ それだけでいいんだ
な？ 簡単だろ？
That's all. Easy, right?
というか
これは いったい何の話だ？
So, uh…
Just what is this all
about anyway?
何って ナルトとヒナタの
結婚祝いで贈る→
新婚旅行の
旅館選びに決まってんだろ。
ふ～ん そうだったのか。
え？
言ってなかったっけ？
ああ 初耳だ。
ええっ ぎゃ～！
それじゃあ また
結婚祝い探しなおすんだ。
うん まあでも
これで よかった気がする。
で シカマルは何があったの？
説明するのも面倒くせえ。
(イルカ)ハハハ…。